dogvacay.com 2015-08-12

# Our Privacy Policy | DogVacay

**_Dog Vacay, Inc._**

**_Privacy Policy_**

Dog Vacay, Inc. (hereafter referred to as "DogVacay" or "DogVacay.com") respects your privacy. Because we gather important information from our users, visitors, subscribers and customers (collectively "you" or "your"), we have established this Privacy Policy as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices. By accessing or using Dogvacay.com (the "Site") or any of our mobile applications or services (the Site, and such applications and services, collectively, "Services"), you acknowledge and agree to this Privacy Policy and also agree to the Terms of Service located at [www.dogvacay.com/terms](https://www.dogvacay.com/terms). We may share information with or among our affiliates or sites that we own or control, but such sharing of information is always governed under the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, and to enable users to enjoy the Services. When you create an account we will set up a DogVacay profile for you. The profile will generally contain your first name, last name initial, location and pet details, and may include other content or information that you provide for purposes of your profile. These profiles will be made available publicly throughout the Site. 

Site Visitor/User Data

a) We collect personal information (such as your name, physical address, phone number and email address) and other information you provide in connection with the provision or improvement of the Services (including to process your listing or respond to a request). Further, if you provide Personal Information for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Information in connection with the reason for which it was provided. When you utilize the Services, we will also collect payment information which is necessary to fulfill your order and taxpayer identification numbers (including in some cases, social security numbers where applicable) to fulfill obligations under applicable state or federal laws or regulations. All personally identifiable information shall be collectively referred to hereafter as "Personal Information." If you fill out a Contact Us form or email us, we will use that information to respond to your request. 

Your Personal Information will not be distributed or shared with third parties unless it is (a) to transact such business as you have contracted us to do (e.g., if you are a host, we will share your Personal Information with users who book a reservation with you or with whom you agree to conduct a Meet-n-Greet) or otherwise to provide the Services (e.g., we may share your Personal Information with our service providers, consultants, agents and representatives in order to perform certain functions on our behalf), (b) to comply with any applicable state or federal laws or regulations, legal processes or obligations and/or law enforcement requests, protect and defend the rights or property of DogVacay, act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or protect against legal liability, (c) in order to conduct any business as we, in our sole subjective discretion, deem reasonable, or (d) in connection with a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event in which Personal Information is part of the transferred assets. In addition, as noted above, any Personal Information included in your profile will be available to the public and we may share your Personal Information with our affiliates. 

We may also use your Personal Information or other information to contact you in the future to tell you about products or services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future marketing communications. 

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Information, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Information to us, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Information may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of DogVacay and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States. 

b) We collect and store Personal Information automatically and in the aggregate. We use the information that we collect to provide and maintain the Services as we deem appropriate in our sole discretion. When you visit or use the Services, we may store some or all of the following: the IP address from which you access the Services, the date and time, the IP address of the web site from which you linked to the Services, the name of the file or words you searched on our Site, items clicked on a page and the browser and operating system used. This information is used to measure the number of visitors to the various sections of our Site and identify system performance. 

c) We use Persistent Cookies to gain aggregate metrics on site usage to understand how people are using the Site and how we can make it better. You may have software on your computer that will allow you to decline or deactivate Internet cookies, but if you do so, some features of the Services may not work properly for you. For instructions on how to remove cookies from your hard drive, go to your browser options. 

We use web metrics services to track activity on the Services. We use this information to help us develop the Services, analyze patterns of usage, and to make Services more useful. This information is not used for associating search terms or patterns of site navigation with individual users. 

Children

We do not knowingly allow any visitors or users under the age of eighteen (18) to use or otherwise access to the Services. We do not wish to collect any Personal Information (or any information at all) from any persons under 18 years old. If you are under 18 years old, you may not use the Services. 

Security

Please note that data that is transported over an open network, such as the Internet or e-mail, may be accessible to anybody. We cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted via such open networks. When disclosing any personal information via an open network, you should remain mindful of the fact that it is potentially accessible to others, and consequently, can be collected and used by others without your consent. Your data may be lost during transmission or may be accessed by unauthorized parties. We do not accept any liability for direct or indirect losses as regards the security of your Personal Information or data during its transfer via Internet. Please use other means of communication if you think this is necessary or prudent for security reasons. 

For network security purposes and to ensure that our Services remain available to all users, we employ commercial software programs to monitor network traffic and attempt to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. All payment information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, encrypted into our payment gateway, and accessible only by those authorized with special access rights to such systems who are required to keep the information confidential. 

External Site Links

DogVacay may link to third party websites or services which may include or offer third party products or services. When you access a linked site you may be disclosing private information. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. DogVacay does not control or guarantee the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, or completeness of information contained on a third party website or service and does not have responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these websites or services. If you click a link to a third party website or service, you will leave the Services and are subject to the privacy and security policies of the owners/sponsors of the third party website or service and not this Privacy Policy. DogVacay cannot authorize the use of copyrighted materials contained in linked websites or services. Users must request such authorization from the sponsor of the linked website or service. DogVacay is not responsible for transmissions users receive from linked websites or services. 

Prohibitions

DogVacay will not willfully or intentionally link to any website that exhibits hate, bias, or discrimination. DogVacay reserves the right to deny or remove any link for any reason. We seek to protect the integrity of our Services at all times and welcome any feedback. 

Exclusions

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Information collected by DogVacay other than Personal Information collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to DogVacay through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as reviews, any ideas for new products or services or modifications to existing products or services, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information"). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and DogVacay shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution. 

Consent and Opt Out

By using our Services, you consent to our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or you wish to Opt Out from receiving any messages we may send you, contact us using the following information: 

**Call:** 855-DOG-VACAY (364 -8222)  
**Email:** [help@dogvacay.com](mailto:help@dogvacay.com)  
**US Mail:**  
Dog Vacay, Inc.  
820 Broadway  
Santa Monica, CA 90401 

Changes To Our Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make changes to this Privacy Policy, they are reflected on this page. Any revised Privacy Policy will apply both to information we already have about you at the time of the change, and any information created or received after the change takes effect. We strongly recommend that you periodically reread this Privacy Policy, to see if there have been any changes to our policies that may affect you. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy. 

_This policy was last modified on November  21, 2013._  
_Click here for our Terms of Service[www.dogvacay.com/terms](http://dogvacay.com/terms)_
